Guide to the Ivy Network Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Ivy Network records
1953-1973
RU 838
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.25
(4 boxes)
The records consist of minutes, tax information, financial statements, correspondence, and subject files documenting the activities and operations of the Ivy Network, an umbrella organization for student-operated radio stations at Ivy League schools.
Ivy Network
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, tax information, financial statements, correspondence, and subject files documenting the activities and operations of the Ivy Network, an umbrella organization for student-operated radio stations at Ivy League schools.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject
College radio stations; Ivy Network
- Records, circa 1953-1973; Accession 1989-A-049
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Service Agreements, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes:
    - 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Spring Meeting, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Market Information, etc.:
    - Promotional Material, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Under 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - National Educational Advertising Services:
    - General, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Copies of Affidavits, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence to and from, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Campus Media
    - 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Orders, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - United Press International:
    - 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Station Payments
    - 1965-1967 and Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Fall and Winter 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Spring 1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Fall 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Winter 1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Spring 1971 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Summer 1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Fall 1971 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Spring 1972 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Fall 1972 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Winter 1972 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Spring 1973 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Winter 1973 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Debit memos, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Station Payments: WBC, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Broadcast Affidavits and Other Advertising Material:
    - Representative Sample of Affidavits and other Material, 1963-1973 (Box 2, Folder 53 - 55)
    - Affidavits: Current, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Tax Information
    - 1960 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - 1961 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - 1971 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Forms and Information, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Audit, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Audit, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Audit, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Financial Statements
    - Year End 1/31, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Year End 1/31, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Year End 1/31, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Year End 1/31, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Year End 1/31, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Year End 1/31, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Nine Months End 10/31, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Year End 1/31, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Nine Months End 10/31, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Year End 1/31, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Five Months End 6/30, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Five Months End 6/30, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Six Months End 12/31, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Six Months End 12/31, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Year End 6/30, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Six Months End 12/31, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Year End 6/30, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Six Months End 12/31, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Year End 6/30, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Six Months End 12/31, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Year End 6/30, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Year End 6/30, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Year End 6/30, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Six Months End 12/31, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Year End 6/30, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Year End 6/30, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Year End 6/30, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Newsletters:
    - 1971-1972 and Undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence
    - Hoffman Stuff, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Sandy L. Maier, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Jim Katz, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Incoming, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - From Stations, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Board Meeting Announcement, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Notices, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Outgoing, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Requests for Information, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Ivy to Stations, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Guild Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Ivy Work, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - sales Leads, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Brochure Replies, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Dore, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Stations to Ivy, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Radio Time Sales, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Posner, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Collegiate Advertising, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Evatone-Evatype, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Other, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Other Business Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Miscellaneous Loose Correspondence:
      - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 121)
      - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 122)
      - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 123)
      - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 124 - 125)
      - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 126)
      - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 127)
      - 1969 (Box 2, Folder 128)
      - 1970 (Box 2, Folder 129)
      - 1971 (Box 2, Folder 130)
      - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 131)
      - 1973 (Box 3, Folder 132)
      - 1974 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Internal Operations
    - Advertising (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Office Services: Public Relations Stuff Available to Us, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Notary Public, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Credit Applications, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Office Equipment, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Remodeling Information and Receipts, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Security, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Misceflaneous Scheduling, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Representative Sample of Contracts, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Representative Sample of Invoices, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Expense Vouchers, Records (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Files on Specific Stations
    - WYBC (Yale), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - WDCR (Dartmouth), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - WBRU (Brown), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - WDCR (Dartmouth), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - WESU (Wesleyan), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - WHRB (Harvard), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - WKCR (Columbia), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - WLRN (Lehigh), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - WMS (Williams), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - WPRB (Princeton), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - WRSU (Rutgers), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - WRUC (Union), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - WTBU (Boston University), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - WTBS (M.I.T.), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - WVBC (Boston college), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - WBR (Cornell), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - WXPN (Pennsylvania), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - WBRU (Brown), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - WRSU (Rutgers), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - WMS (Williams), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - WRUC (Union), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - WKCR (Columbia), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - WLRN (Lehigh), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - WPRB (Princeton), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - WVBC (Boston College), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - WTBS (M.I.T.), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - WTBU (Boston University), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - WVBR (Cornell), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - WXPN (Pennsylvania), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - WHRB (Harvard), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - WYBC (Yale), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - WPRB (Princeton), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - WYBC (Yale), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - WXPN (Pennsylvania), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - WBR (Cornell), 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - WVBC (Boston College), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - WRUC (Union), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - WTBS (M.I.T.), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - WTBU (Boston University), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - WRSU (Rutgers), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - WMS (Williams), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - WLRN (Lehigh), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - WKCR (Columbia), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - WHRB (Harvard), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - WESU (Wesleyan), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - WDCR (Dartmouth), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - WBRU (Brown), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - WBRU (Brown), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - WDCR (Dartmouth), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - WESU (Wesleyan), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - WESU (Wesleyan), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - WHRB (Harvard), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - WKCR (Columbia), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - WMS (Williams), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - WLRN (Lehigh), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - WPRB (Princeton), 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - WRSU (Rutgers), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - WRUC (Union), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - WTBS (M.I.T.), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - WTBU (Boston University), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - WVBR (Cornell), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - WVBC (Boston College), 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - WXPN (Pennsylvania), 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Miscellaneous:
    - Reuters, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Alumni, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Penalties, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1970 (Box 4, Folder 212)